https://www.exceltemplates.com/privacy-policy

CalendarsChartsAccounting & FinancialProject Management TemplatesSchedulingBudgetSheet TemplatesOthersAboutContact UspCalendarsChartsAccounting & FinancialProject Management TemplatesSchedulingBudgetSheet TemplatesOthersPrivacy PolicyPRIVACY POLICYHere at ExcelTemplate.com, your privacy is a priority. We respect your right to know how your information is collected and used. Rest assured, your details are safe with us and are exclusive to the services we use to host and manage our website. Outside parties will have no access to your information.This website owns and manages itself. Any use of the words “we,” “us,” or “our” refers to us and those that help us run ExcelTemplates.com – our associates, employees, and affiliates.This policy applies to all those who visit and use the services of this site. Submission, download, or access of contents on ExcelTemplates.com signify that you agree with the terms and conditions of our website.COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL DATAWe may gather and use personal information to provide you with better customer experience. These data are composed of the information you provided us upon sign up or when using our website’s services, such as your name, contact information, email address, username, etc.We may also collect your online activity information (login and log out times, visited pages, etc.)  and technical information (IP address, OS type, and version, etc.) to make sure that our website and services are working properly.Exceltemplates.com does not share its email listings or any personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your data in good faith for legal and investigative purposes.COOKIESExceltemplate.com uses cookies to distinguish users from one another. Cookies are information stored in your device that helps us recognize the device you’re using, track your activity, and collect information that we can use to enhance your browsing experience.You can choose not to accept the cookies by changing your browser settings, but doing so might cause you some inconveniences while browsing.ACCESSING AND USING OUR CONTENTExceltemplates.com exercise ownership and copyright of all forms of content and information within this website. Selling or making a profit from our contents is against the law. Our materials are intended for non-commercial uses only.Those who are found reproducing, republishing, distributing, or exploiting the materials on this website may face legal consequences.CONTENT SUBMISSIONS TO OUR SITEContents submitted to exceltemplates.com are subject to evaluation and approval. We reserve the right to choose which submissions to publish or not publish on our website.By submitting contents to exceltemplates.com, you hereby grant us (as well as our partners and affiliates) the right to modify, reuse, and redistribute said materials in whatever way or purpose we see fit.Moreover, you agree to take full responsibility for your submission. You will be held accountable for any laws, rules, and terms of use violated by the content you submitted.CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYThis privacy policy may be amended at any time to reflect changes in our practices. Any alterations that we make will be posted here and will take effect after the update has been made.Please review this policy from time to time to keep track of modifications.CONTACT USFor questions regarding our Privacy Policy, contact us here.Our TemplatesSheet TemplatesWorksheet TemplatesExpense SheetsBalance Sheet TemplateCover Sheet TemplateSpec Sheet TemplateSign in Sheet TemplateCharacter Sheet TemplateFact Sheet TemplateTime Sheet TemplateReference Sheet TemplateAttendence Sheet TemplateTerm Sheet TemplatePrice Sheet TemplateSafety Data Sheet TemplateOthersSuper Bowl SquaresWedding TemplatesWorkout TemplatesPro Forma TemplatesPassword TrackerFamily TreeFantasy FootballGrocery List TemplatesBlood Sugar LogBudgetPersonal Budget TemplateSales Reports TemplateExpense ReportDebt Payoff SpreadsheetCheck Register TemplateBudget Worksheet TemplateProject ManagementAction Plan TemplateProject Budget TemplateProject Plan TemplateProject Schedule TemplateProject Status Report TemplateProject Timeline TemplateProject TrackingSchedulingAccounting & FinancialPurchase Order TemplatesIncome Statement TemplateFinancial Statement TemplateGeneral Ledger TemplateBreak Even Analysis TemplateFree Excel ChartsBusiness Chart TemplatesGANTT Chart TemplatesMore Chart TemplatesOrganizational Chart TemplatesWeight Loss Chart TemplatesOther Free Excel TemplatesFree Printable CalendarsMonthly Calendar TemplatesMore Calendar Templates2020 Calendar TemplatesBusiness Calendar TemplatesSchool Calendar TemplatesWeekly Calendar TemplatesDaily Calendar Templates
AboutPrivacy PolicyContact Us@ 2018 ExcelTemplates. All rights reversed.
